gridironsoftware.com 2012-09-25

# FileTrek Privacy Policy

## Table of Contents

  1. Introduction
  2. Information We Collect Directly From You
  3. Information We Collect from Your Use of Our Website
  4. How We Use the Information We Collect
  5. Sharing of Your Information
  6. Our Policies Concerning Children
  7. How to Access and Update Your Information
  8. Privacy Policies of Linked Sites and Advertisers
  9. Security of Your Information
  10. Changes to Our Privacy Policy
  11. Your California Privacy Rights
  12. Contact Us

## I. Introduction

FileTrek is a software provider of mobile content management and tracking solutions for complete visibility of sharing, syncing and versioning activities on the desktop and in the cloud. We provide solutions for tracking, editing and hosting documents in real time for companies of all sizes (the “Service”). In this policy, "FileTrek" refers to FileTrek Inc. and its Affiliates, which shall mean subsidiaries, parent companies, joint ventures and other corporate entities under common ownership. We may also refer to FileTrek as "we" or "us".

This Privacy Policy describes:

  * the information we collect, how we do so and the purposes of our collection
  * how we use and with whom we share such information
  * how you can access and update such information
  * the choices you can make about how we collect, use and share your information
  * how we protect the information we store about you

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy or our collection and use of information, please contact us as described in Section 13 ("Contact Us").

## II. Information We Collect Directly From You

**Information We Collect from You Directly**

When you interact with the Service, at www.filetrek.com (the “Website”), we may collect and store information from you directly as described below:

**Registration Information**

You may register with Us by providing the following information: your age or birth date (for age screening and/or to better understand who our users are); your first and last name; user name and password; your email address and your company affiliation and other information that helps Us confirm that it is you accessing your account.

**Payment Information**

If you purchase a subscription to the Services, we will collect the billing and financial information necessary to process your charges, which may include your postal and email addresses. Our Subscription and License Agreement explain our policies and terms relevant to our charges and billing practices.

**Customer Support Correspondence**

When you ask for assistance from our Customer Support team, we will collect and store the contact information you provide (generally your name and email address), information about your activity on the Service, and your user ID number. We will also store the correspondence and any information contained within.

**Technical and Usage Information**

When you access our Website, we collect (i) certain technical information about your mobile device or computer system, including IP Address and mobile device ID; and (ii) usage statistics about your interactions with the Service. This information is typically collected through the use of server log files or web log files (“Log Files”), mobile device software development kits and tracking technologies like browser cookies to collect and analyze certain types of technical information. Some of the cookies the Service places on your computer are linked to your user ID number(s). For more information on how we utilize cookies and other tracking technologies please review the "Cookies and Automated Information Collection" portion of Section 4 ("Information We Collect From Your Use of Our Website").

## III. Information We Collect From Your Use of Our Website

We may collect information about you in any one or more of the following ways:

**Communications Features**

You may be able to take part in certain activities on our Website that give you the opportunity to communicate or share information not just with FileTrek, but also with other users of our Service. These include:

  * sending messages or invitations to other users, either directly on our Website or to their email accounts

We may record and store archives of these communications on FileTrek's servers to protect the safety and well being of our users and FileTrek's rights and property in connection with the service. You acknowledge and consent to the recording and storage of such communications for these purposes.

**Cookies and Automated Information Collection**

When you access the Service, we collect certain technical information in order to (i) analyze the usage of our site and services and (ii) provide a more personalized experience. We and service providers acting on our behalf use Log Files and tracking technologies to collect and analyze certain types of technical information, including cookies, IP addresses, device type, device identifiers, browser types, browser language, referring and exit pages, and URLs, platform type, the number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages and other similar information. In some cases, we will associate this information with your user ID number for our internal use.

You can set your web browser to warn you about attempts to place cookies on your computer or limit the type of cookies you allow. Flash cookies operate differently than browser cookies and cookie management tools available in a web browser may not remove flash cookies. To learn more about and manage flash cookies you can visit adobe.com and make changes at the privacy settings panel. If you disable cookies, you may lose some of the features and functionality of playing our Service, as FileTrek cookies are necessary to track and enhance your Service.

**The Application and Metadata**

We provide you with software to facilitate the monitoring, collection, recording and transmission of your data and to the Service (the “Application”). When you install the Application on your computer or other device, the Application will automatically monitor, record, collect and transmit information about your data, including without limitation the means of creation, purpose, time and date of creation, creator or author of data, placement on a network, access to such data on the network by users, date and time for such access, modifications to such asset, and sources of content elements, as collected by the Service (the “Metadata”). For a complete list of the all Metadata currently being captures and stored by us, please see the Metadata Captured portion of our site. We use the Metadata collected solely in connection with our operation of the Service.

Once the Application has been installed on your computer or device, it shall continue to monitor, record, collect and transmit Metadata until you uninstall the Application or otherwise render it inoperable. This can be accomplished by either logging out of the Application or uninstalling it on your computer or device.

## IV. How We Use the Information We Collect

In general, we collect, store and use your information to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. For example, we may use information collected from you in any one or more of the following ways:

  * to enable user-to-user communications
  * to provide technical support and respond to user inquiries
  * to prevent fraud or potentially illegal activities, and enforce our Subscription and License Agreement
  * to solicit input and feedback to improve our products and services and customize your user experience

## V. Sharing of Your Information

We will share your information (in some cases personal information) with third parties, that is parties other than FileTrek, in the following circumstances:

**Third Party Service Providers**

We will provide your information to third party companies to perform services on our behalf, including payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services and customer service. We direct all such third party service providers to maintain the confidentiality of the information disclosed to them and to not use your information for any purpose other than to provide services on FileTrek's behalf.

**Safety, Security and Compliance with Law**

Your information, and the contents of all of your online communications (including without limitation chat text, IP addresses and your personal information) may be accessed and monitored as necessary to provide the Service and may be disclosed: (i) when we have a good faith belief that we are required to disclose the information in response to legal process (for example, a court order, search warrant or subpoena); (ii) to satisfy any applicable laws or regulations (iii) where we believe that the Service is being used in the commission of a crime, including to report such criminal activity or to exchange information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction; (iv) when we have a good faith belief that there is an emergency that poses a threat to the health and/or safety of you, another person or the public generally; and (v) in order to protect the rights or property of FileTrek, including to enforce our Subscription and License Agreement.

**Sale or Merger**

In the event that FileTrek undergoes a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, we may transfer all of your information, including personal information, to the successor organization in such transition. If material changes to FileTrek's privacy practices will occur as a result of the business transition, we will notify you and other users (in the manner described in Section 11) of the business transition prior to transferring your personal information.

## VI. Our Policies Concerning Children

Our Website is not intended for children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from such children. Children under the age of 13 should not use our Website at any time. In the event that we learn that we have inadvertently gathered personal information from children under the age of 13, we will take reasonable measures to promptly erase such information from our records.

## VII. How to Access and Update Your Information

**Other Methods of Accessing and Controlling your Information**

  * If you no longer want FileTrek to make active use of your information, you may send an email to privacy@filetrek.com. Place "Delete My Account" in the subject line and include your first name, last name, email address in the body of the email. We will respond to your request within thirty (30) days. Please note that certain records, for example those pertaining to payments or customer service matters, will be retained for legal and accounting purposes. If you have sent or posted content on the Service, we may not be able to delete it.
  * If you wish to review or change the information FileTrek has about you, email Us at the address provided herein.
  * If you have additional questions about this Privacy Policy, contact us at privacy@filetrek.com.

## VIII. Privacy Policies of Linked Sites and Advertisers

Our Website may contain links to third party websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. If you have any questions about how these other websites use your information, you should review their policies and contact them directly.

## IX. Security of Your Information

FileTrek implements reasonable security measures to protect the security of your information both online and offline, and we are committed to the protection of customer information.

For user accounts registered directly with FileTrek profile information is protected by the password each member uses to access their online account. It is important that you protect and maintain the security of your account and that you immediately notify Us of any unauthorized use of your account. If you forget the password to your FileTrek account, our Website allows you to request that instructions be sent to you that explain how to reset your password. When you sign into your account or enter payment information (such as a credit card number when purchasing virtual currency), we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology ("SSL").

While we take reasonable precautions against possible security breaches of our Website and our customer databases and records, no website or Internet transmission is completely secure, and we cannot guarantee that unauthorized access, hacking, data loss, or other breaches will never occur. We urge you to take steps to keep your information safe (including your account password), and to log out of your account after use. If you have questions about the security of our Website, please contact us at privacy@filetrek.com.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information over the Internet is not completely secure. Although we strive to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data while it is being transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we have procedures and security features in place to try to prevent unauthorized access.

## X. Changes to Our Privacy Policy

If we decide to make material changes to our Privacy Policy, we will notify you and other users by placing a notice on filetrek.com or by sending you a notice to the email address we have on file for you. You should periodically check www.filetrek.com and this privacy page for updates.

## XI. Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. As detailed in our Privacy Policy, we do not share our customer's personal information with third parties for direct marketing purposes. However, if you nonetheless desire to make such an inquiry, please send us an email at [privacy@filetrek.com](mailto:privacy@filetrek.com).

## XII. Contact Us

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy and/or practices, please send an email to [privacy@filetrek.com](mailto:privacy@filetrek.com). All other inquiries should be directed to FileTrek's [support page](http://support.filetrek.com/).

FileTrek Software Inc.  
350 S. Figueroa St. Suite 233  
Los Angeles, CA 90071, USA
